{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775992708","data":{"timestamp":" 947775992707"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 4401013a-70dc-464f-90d0-9816787279bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_1+1"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947775999783","data":{"timestamp":" 947775999783"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 4401013a-70dc-464f-90d0-9816787279bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_1+1"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776012399","data":{"timestamp":" 947776012399"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 5cac2522-1daf-4945-a9cf-02ca8ad943eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mpi_mpi-bwa-cha"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mpi"," userResponse":" mpi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776022020","data":{"timestamp":" 947776022020"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 5cac2522-1daf-4945-a9cf-02ca8ad943eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nja_mwo-vya-nja"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nja"," userResponse":" nja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776029628","data":{"timestamp":" 947776029628"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 5cac2522-1daf-4945-a9cf-02ca8ad943eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mki_mgo-mke-mki"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mki"," userResponse":" mki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776034880","data":{"timestamp":" 947776034880"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 5cac2522-1daf-4945-a9cf-02ca8ad943eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mzu_mme-dha-mzu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mzu"," userResponse":" mzu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776040882","data":{"timestamp":" 947776040882"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 5cac2522-1daf-4945-a9cf-02ca8ad943eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mgu_nje-nja-mgu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mgu"," userResponse":" mgu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776046142","data":{"timestamp":" 947776046141"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 5cac2522-1daf-4945-a9cf-02ca8ad943eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mta_nji-mno-mta"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mta"," userResponse":" mta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776051710","data":{"timestamp":" 947776051709"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 5cac2522-1daf-4945-a9cf-02ca8ad943eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_thi_njo-swa-thi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" thi"," userResponse":" thi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776057670","data":{"timestamp":" 947776057670"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 5cac2522-1daf-4945-a9cf-02ca8ad943eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nji_bwa-nji-mfa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nji"," userResponse":" nji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776062720","data":{"timestamp":" 947776062719"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 5cac2522-1daf-4945-a9cf-02ca8ad943eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nde_kwa-mwi-nde"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nde"," userResponse":" nde"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776068717","data":{"timestamp":" 947776068717"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 5cac2522-1daf-4945-a9cf-02ca8ad943eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ndu_ndu-chi-nyi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ndu"," userResponse":" ndu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776074460","data":{"timestamp":" 947776074460"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 5cac2522-1daf-4945-a9cf-02ca8ad943eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_ndu_ndu-chi-nyi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776114379","data":{"timestamp":" 947776114379"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 5cac2522-1daf-4945-a9cf-02ca8ad943eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_ndu_ndu-chi-nyi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.kwu..kwu.noShow..24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776135719","data":{"timestamp":" 947776135719"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" c297fd4b-b33b-49db-8dbc-7a505981d072"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.kwu..kwu.noShow..24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_msi_kwu_du"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.kwu..kwu.noShow..24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776142404","data":{"timestamp":" 947776142403"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" c297fd4b-b33b-49db-8dbc-7a505981d072"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.kwu..kwu.noShow..24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_twa_mba_kwu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.kwu..kwu.noShow..24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776149064","data":{"timestamp":" 947776149064"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" c297fd4b-b33b-49db-8dbc-7a505981d072"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.kwu..kwu.noShow..24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kwu_shi_ro"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.kwu..kwu.noShow..24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776155704","data":{"timestamp":" 947776155703"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" c297fd4b-b33b-49db-8dbc-7a505981d072"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.kwu..kwu.noShow..24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_go_kwu_shu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.kwu..kwu.noShow..24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776162383","data":{"timestamp":" 947776162383"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" c297fd4b-b33b-49db-8dbc-7a505981d072"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.kwu..kwu.noShow..24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_sho_mbe_kwu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.kwu..kwu.noShow..24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776169039","data":{"timestamp":" 947776169039"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" c297fd4b-b33b-49db-8dbc-7a505981d072"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.kwu..kwu.noShow..24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_gi_jo_kwu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.kwu..kwu.noShow..24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776175719","data":{"timestamp":" 947776175719"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" c297fd4b-b33b-49db-8dbc-7a505981d072"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.kwu..kwu.noShow..24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nu_kwu_ku"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.kwu..kwu.noShow..24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776182458","data":{"timestamp":" 947776182457"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" c297fd4b-b33b-49db-8dbc-7a505981d072"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.kwu..kwu.noShow..24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_wi_kwu_ma"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.kwu..kwu.noShow..24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776189121","data":{"timestamp":" 947776189121"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" c297fd4b-b33b-49db-8dbc-7a505981d072"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.kwu..kwu.noShow..24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mba_yo_kwu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.kwu..kwu.noShow..24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776195798","data":{"timestamp":" 947776195798"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" c297fd4b-b33b-49db-8dbc-7a505981d072"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.kwu..kwu.noShow..24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mna_cho_kwu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.kwu..kwu.noShow..24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776209087","data":{"timestamp":" 947776209085"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" c297fd4b-b33b-49db-8dbc-7a505981d072"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.kwu..kwu.noShow..24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_mna_cho_kwu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776215799","data":{"timestamp":" 947776215799"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" c297fd4b-b33b-49db-8dbc-7a505981d072"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.kwu..kwu.noShow..24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_mna_cho_kwu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:kwu..kwu.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.71","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776229223","data":{"timestamp":" 947776229223"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" c297fd4b-b33b-49db-8dbc-7a505981d072"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.kwu..kwu.noShow..24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_mna_cho_kwu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776238326","data":{"timestamp":" 947776238325"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" c297fd4b-b33b-49db-8dbc-7a505981d072"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.kwu..kwu.noShow..24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_mna_cho_kwu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776249260","data":{"timestamp":" 947776249260"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" fe287f06-4389-4ffc-9ec7-d065e2b69e46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mna_mwu-vyo-mna"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mna"," userResponse":" mna"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776255463","data":{"timestamp":" 947776255463"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" fe287f06-4389-4ffc-9ec7-d065e2b69e46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mza_mwi-mza-mgu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mza"," userResponse":" mza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776261640","data":{"timestamp":" 947776261640"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" fe287f06-4389-4ffc-9ec7-d065e2b69e46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_she_she-vya-nge"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" she"," userResponse":" she"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776268092","data":{"timestamp":" 947776268092"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" fe287f06-4389-4ffc-9ec7-d065e2b69e46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mba_mto-mba-mti"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mba"," userResponse":" mba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776273912","data":{"timestamp":" 947776273912"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" fe287f06-4389-4ffc-9ec7-d065e2b69e46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_cho_mje-cho-mti"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" cho"," userResponse":" cho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776281524","data":{"timestamp":" 947776281524"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" fe287f06-4389-4ffc-9ec7-d065e2b69e46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mna_mna-mle-kwa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mna"," userResponse":" mna"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776287611","data":{"timestamp":" 947776287611"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" fe287f06-4389-4ffc-9ec7-d065e2b69e46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mfa_nde-vye-mfa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mfa"," userResponse":" mfa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776292462","data":{"timestamp":" 947776292462"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" fe287f06-4389-4ffc-9ec7-d065e2b69e46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nju_she-nju-mjo"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nju"," userResponse":" nju"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776297528","data":{"timestamp":" 947776297527"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" fe287f06-4389-4ffc-9ec7-d065e2b69e46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nje_nje-mgo-vyu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nje"," userResponse":" nje"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776304554","data":{"timestamp":" 947776304554"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" fe287f06-4389-4ffc-9ec7-d065e2b69e46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mku_shi-mko-mku"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mku"," userResponse":" mku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776310323","data":{"timestamp":" 947776310323"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" fe287f06-4389-4ffc-9ec7-d065e2b69e46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_mku_shi-mko-mku"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776317016","data":{"timestamp":" 947776317015"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" fe287f06-4389-4ffc-9ec7-d065e2b69e46"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_mku_shi-mko-mku"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.all.stat.show.72","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776332634","data":{"timestamp":" 947776332634"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 1d70e003-33f7-41ce-ac24-cd2e26c11601"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.all.stat.show.72"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_mbi-ro-me"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.all.stat.show.72","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776337330","data":{"timestamp":" 947776337330"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 1d70e003-33f7-41ce-ac24-cd2e26c11601"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.all.stat.show.72"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_mbi-mlo-ti"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.all.stat.show.72","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776342703","data":{"timestamp":" 947776342703"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 1d70e003-33f7-41ce-ac24-cd2e26c11601"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.all.stat.show.72"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_me-mbi-no"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.all.stat.show.72","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776347519","data":{"timestamp":" 947776347518"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 1d70e003-33f7-41ce-ac24-cd2e26c11601"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.all.stat.show.72"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_swa-bwa-mbi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.all.stat.show.72","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776353007","data":{"timestamp":" 947776353007"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 1d70e003-33f7-41ce-ac24-cd2e26c11601"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.all.stat.show.72"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_mbi-so-hi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.all.stat.show.72","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776358374","data":{"timestamp":" 947776358374"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 1d70e003-33f7-41ce-ac24-cd2e26c11601"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.all.stat.show.72"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_twi-mbi-ng'e"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.all.stat.show.72","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776362886","data":{"timestamp":" 947776362886"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 1d70e003-33f7-41ce-ac24-cd2e26c11601"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.all.stat.show.72"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_mbi-ngo-mwu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.all.stat.show.72","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776371142","data":{"timestamp":" 947776371142"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 1d70e003-33f7-41ce-ac24-cd2e26c11601"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.all.stat.show.72"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_mwi-mbi-ng'u"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.all.stat.show.72","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776376308","data":{"timestamp":" 947776376308"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 1d70e003-33f7-41ce-ac24-cd2e26c11601"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.all.stat.show.72"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_je-pe-mbi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.all.stat.show.72","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776381416","data":{"timestamp":" 947776381416"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 1d70e003-33f7-41ce-ac24-cd2e26c11601"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.all.stat.show.72"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_che-mbi-vyu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.all.stat.show.72","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776387205","data":{"timestamp":" 947776387205"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 1d70e003-33f7-41ce-ac24-cd2e26c11601"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.all.stat.show.72"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_che-mbi-vyu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776396343","data":{"timestamp":" 947776396343"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 1d70e003-33f7-41ce-ac24-cd2e26c11601"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.all.stat.show.72"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_che-mbi-vyu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.32__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776409745","data":{"timestamp":" 947776409745"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 3b54eb96-ffe3-42f4-adf9-8033b030d473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.32__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYA"," userResponse":" NYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.32__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776412489","data":{"timestamp":" 947776412489"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 3b54eb96-ffe3-42f4-adf9-8033b030d473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.32__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.32__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776416742","data":{"timestamp":" 947776416720"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 3b54eb96-ffe3-42f4-adf9-8033b030d473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.32__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nye"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYE"," userResponse":" NYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.32__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776419893","data":{"timestamp":" 947776419893"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 3b54eb96-ffe3-42f4-adf9-8033b030d473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.32__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nye"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.32__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776421459","data":{"timestamp":" 947776421459"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 3b54eb96-ffe3-42f4-adf9-8033b030d473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.32__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYI"," userResponse":" NYI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.32__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776424520","data":{"timestamp":" 947776424520"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 3b54eb96-ffe3-42f4-adf9-8033b030d473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.32__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.32__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776426088","data":{"timestamp":" 947776426088"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 3b54eb96-ffe3-42f4-adf9-8033b030d473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.32__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYO"," userResponse":" NYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.32__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776429047","data":{"timestamp":" 947776429047"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 3b54eb96-ffe3-42f4-adf9-8033b030d473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.32__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.32__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776430609","data":{"timestamp":" 947776430609"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 3b54eb96-ffe3-42f4-adf9-8033b030d473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.32__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYU"," userResponse":" NYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.32__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776482410","data":{"timestamp":" 947776482409"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 3b54eb96-ffe3-42f4-adf9-8033b030d473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.32__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYU"," userResponse":" NYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.32__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776484424","data":{"timestamp":" 947776484424"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 3b54eb96-ffe3-42f4-adf9-8033b030d473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.32__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" nyu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947776484616","data":{"timestamp":" 947776484616"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 3b54eb96-ffe3-42f4-adf9-8033b030d473"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.nya..nyu.asc.lc.32__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYU"," userResponse":" NYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947804915990","data":{"timestamp":" 947804915990"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 878fa820-8eb3-4342-a377-db03d8ac6e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947804916213","data":{"timestamp":" 947804916213"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 878fa820-8eb3-4342-a377-db03d8ac6e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947804917177","data":{"timestamp":" 947804917176"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 878fa820-8eb3-4342-a377-db03d8ac6e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947804918451","data":{"timestamp":" 947804918451"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 878fa820-8eb3-4342-a377-db03d8ac6e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947804921337","data":{"timestamp":" 947804921336"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 878fa820-8eb3-4342-a377-db03d8ac6e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947804922180","data":{"timestamp":" 947804922180"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 878fa820-8eb3-4342-a377-db03d8ac6e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947804922495","data":{"timestamp":" 947804922495"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 878fa820-8eb3-4342-a377-db03d8ac6e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947804923728","data":{"timestamp":" 947804923728"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 878fa820-8eb3-4342-a377-db03d8ac6e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947804927244","data":{"timestamp":" 947804927243"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 878fa820-8eb3-4342-a377-db03d8ac6e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947804928227","data":{"timestamp":" 947804928226"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 878fa820-8eb3-4342-a377-db03d8ac6e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947804928480","data":{"timestamp":" 947804928480"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 878fa820-8eb3-4342-a377-db03d8ac6e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947804929425","data":{"timestamp":" 947804929425"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 878fa820-8eb3-4342-a377-db03d8ac6e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947804932272","data":{"timestamp":" 947804932272"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 878fa820-8eb3-4342-a377-db03d8ac6e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947804933306","data":{"timestamp":" 947804933306"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 878fa820-8eb3-4342-a377-db03d8ac6e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947804933782","data":{"timestamp":" 947804933782"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 878fa820-8eb3-4342-a377-db03d8ac6e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947804938317","data":{"timestamp":" 947804938317"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 878fa820-8eb3-4342-a377-db03d8ac6e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947804938433","data":{"timestamp":" 947804938433"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 878fa820-8eb3-4342-a377-db03d8ac6e11"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947804961724","data":{"timestamp":" 947804961723"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 340ed2aa-5cc9-4d41-b42f-b140f08bbc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947804961949","data":{"timestamp":" 947804961949"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 340ed2aa-5cc9-4d41-b42f-b140f08bbc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947804962914","data":{"timestamp":" 947804962914"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 340ed2aa-5cc9-4d41-b42f-b140f08bbc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947804964189","data":{"timestamp":" 947804964188"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 340ed2aa-5cc9-4d41-b42f-b140f08bbc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947804967073","data":{"timestamp":" 947804967073"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 340ed2aa-5cc9-4d41-b42f-b140f08bbc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947804967917","data":{"timestamp":" 947804967917"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 340ed2aa-5cc9-4d41-b42f-b140f08bbc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947804968231","data":{"timestamp":" 947804968231"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 340ed2aa-5cc9-4d41-b42f-b140f08bbc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947804969466","data":{"timestamp":" 947804969465"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 340ed2aa-5cc9-4d41-b42f-b140f08bbc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947804972987","data":{"timestamp":" 947804972987"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 340ed2aa-5cc9-4d41-b42f-b140f08bbc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947804973973","data":{"timestamp":" 947804973973"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 340ed2aa-5cc9-4d41-b42f-b140f08bbc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947804974227","data":{"timestamp":" 947804974227"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 340ed2aa-5cc9-4d41-b42f-b140f08bbc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947804975172","data":{"timestamp":" 947804975172"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 340ed2aa-5cc9-4d41-b42f-b140f08bbc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947804978028","data":{"timestamp":" 947804978028"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 340ed2aa-5cc9-4d41-b42f-b140f08bbc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947804979062","data":{"timestamp":" 947804979062"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 340ed2aa-5cc9-4d41-b42f-b140f08bbc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947804979536","data":{"timestamp":" 947804979536"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 340ed2aa-5cc9-4d41-b42f-b140f08bbc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947804984069","data":{"timestamp":" 947804984068"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 340ed2aa-5cc9-4d41-b42f-b140f08bbc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947804984155","data":{"timestamp":" 947804984155"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 340ed2aa-5cc9-4d41-b42f-b140f08bbc64"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805017043","data":{"timestamp":" 947805017043"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 14c1d729-2543-43ad-80cd-469c96d6d985"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805017268","data":{"timestamp":" 947805017267"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 14c1d729-2543-43ad-80cd-469c96d6d985"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805018232","data":{"timestamp":" 947805018232"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 14c1d729-2543-43ad-80cd-469c96d6d985"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805019506","data":{"timestamp":" 947805019506"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 14c1d729-2543-43ad-80cd-469c96d6d985"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805022392","data":{"timestamp":" 947805022391"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 14c1d729-2543-43ad-80cd-469c96d6d985"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805023236","data":{"timestamp":" 947805023235"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 14c1d729-2543-43ad-80cd-469c96d6d985"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805023549","data":{"timestamp":" 947805023549"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 14c1d729-2543-43ad-80cd-469c96d6d985"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805024783","data":{"timestamp":" 947805024783"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 14c1d729-2543-43ad-80cd-469c96d6d985"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805028293","data":{"timestamp":" 947805028293"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 14c1d729-2543-43ad-80cd-469c96d6d985"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805029278","data":{"timestamp":" 947805029278"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 14c1d729-2543-43ad-80cd-469c96d6d985"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805029532","data":{"timestamp":" 947805029531"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 14c1d729-2543-43ad-80cd-469c96d6d985"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805030475","data":{"timestamp":" 947805030474"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 14c1d729-2543-43ad-80cd-469c96d6d985"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805033316","data":{"timestamp":" 947805033316"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 14c1d729-2543-43ad-80cd-469c96d6d985"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805034350","data":{"timestamp":" 947805034349"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 14c1d729-2543-43ad-80cd-469c96d6d985"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805034824","data":{"timestamp":" 947805034823"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 14c1d729-2543-43ad-80cd-469c96d6d985"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805039349","data":{"timestamp":" 947805039348"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 14c1d729-2543-43ad-80cd-469c96d6d985"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805039499","data":{"timestamp":" 947805039499"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 14c1d729-2543-43ad-80cd-469c96d6d985"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805066293","data":{"timestamp":" 947805066293"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" ec37479c-1a68-4ed5-b092-16915fcebb08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805066517","data":{"timestamp":" 947805066517"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" ec37479c-1a68-4ed5-b092-16915fcebb08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805067483","data":{"timestamp":" 947805067482"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" ec37479c-1a68-4ed5-b092-16915fcebb08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805068757","data":{"timestamp":" 947805068756"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" ec37479c-1a68-4ed5-b092-16915fcebb08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805071636","data":{"timestamp":" 947805071636"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" ec37479c-1a68-4ed5-b092-16915fcebb08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805072480","data":{"timestamp":" 947805072480"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" ec37479c-1a68-4ed5-b092-16915fcebb08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805072794","data":{"timestamp":" 947805072794"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" ec37479c-1a68-4ed5-b092-16915fcebb08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805074029","data":{"timestamp":" 947805074029"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" ec37479c-1a68-4ed5-b092-16915fcebb08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805077534","data":{"timestamp":" 947805077534"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" ec37479c-1a68-4ed5-b092-16915fcebb08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805078519","data":{"timestamp":" 947805078519"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" ec37479c-1a68-4ed5-b092-16915fcebb08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805078773","data":{"timestamp":" 947805078773"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" ec37479c-1a68-4ed5-b092-16915fcebb08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805079717","data":{"timestamp":" 947805079717"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" ec37479c-1a68-4ed5-b092-16915fcebb08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805082581","data":{"timestamp":" 947805082581"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" ec37479c-1a68-4ed5-b092-16915fcebb08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805083616","data":{"timestamp":" 947805083616"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" ec37479c-1a68-4ed5-b092-16915fcebb08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805084090","data":{"timestamp":" 947805084090"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" ec37479c-1a68-4ed5-b092-16915fcebb08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805088620","data":{"timestamp":" 947805088620"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" ec37479c-1a68-4ed5-b092-16915fcebb08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805088721","data":{"timestamp":" 947805088721"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" ec37479c-1a68-4ed5-b092-16915fcebb08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805102458","data":{"timestamp":" 947805102457"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 418d095c-c1c6-4c25-a4ad-741255eca538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805102682","data":{"timestamp":" 947805102681"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 418d095c-c1c6-4c25-a4ad-741255eca538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805103646","data":{"timestamp":" 947805103646"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 418d095c-c1c6-4c25-a4ad-741255eca538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805104919","data":{"timestamp":" 947805104918"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 418d095c-c1c6-4c25-a4ad-741255eca538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805107803","data":{"timestamp":" 947805107803"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 418d095c-c1c6-4c25-a4ad-741255eca538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805108648","data":{"timestamp":" 947805108648"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 418d095c-c1c6-4c25-a4ad-741255eca538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805108966","data":{"timestamp":" 947805108965"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 418d095c-c1c6-4c25-a4ad-741255eca538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805110203","data":{"timestamp":" 947805110203"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 418d095c-c1c6-4c25-a4ad-741255eca538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805113721","data":{"timestamp":" 947805113720"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 418d095c-c1c6-4c25-a4ad-741255eca538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805114707","data":{"timestamp":" 947805114706"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 418d095c-c1c6-4c25-a4ad-741255eca538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805114967","data":{"timestamp":" 947805114967"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 418d095c-c1c6-4c25-a4ad-741255eca538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805115914","data":{"timestamp":" 947805115914"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 418d095c-c1c6-4c25-a4ad-741255eca538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805118787","data":{"timestamp":" 947805118787"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 418d095c-c1c6-4c25-a4ad-741255eca538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805119834","data":{"timestamp":" 947805119834"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 418d095c-c1c6-4c25-a4ad-741255eca538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805120307","data":{"timestamp":" 947805120307"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 418d095c-c1c6-4c25-a4ad-741255eca538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805124856","data":{"timestamp":" 947805124856"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 418d095c-c1c6-4c25-a4ad-741255eca538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805124959","data":{"timestamp":" 947805124959"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 418d095c-c1c6-4c25-a4ad-741255eca538"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805329839","data":{"timestamp":" 947805329839"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 5a4a5ea4-7ade-46fc-a436-d82a16101216"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805330064","data":{"timestamp":" 947805330064"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 5a4a5ea4-7ade-46fc-a436-d82a16101216"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805331028","data":{"timestamp":" 947805331028"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 5a4a5ea4-7ade-46fc-a436-d82a16101216"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805332302","data":{"timestamp":" 947805332302"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 5a4a5ea4-7ade-46fc-a436-d82a16101216"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805335203","data":{"timestamp":" 947805335203"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 5a4a5ea4-7ade-46fc-a436-d82a16101216"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805336047","data":{"timestamp":" 947805336047"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 5a4a5ea4-7ade-46fc-a436-d82a16101216"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805336362","data":{"timestamp":" 947805336362"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 5a4a5ea4-7ade-46fc-a436-d82a16101216"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805337595","data":{"timestamp":" 947805337595"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 5a4a5ea4-7ade-46fc-a436-d82a16101216"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805341114","data":{"timestamp":" 947805341114"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 5a4a5ea4-7ade-46fc-a436-d82a16101216"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805342099","data":{"timestamp":" 947805342099"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 5a4a5ea4-7ade-46fc-a436-d82a16101216"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805342356","data":{"timestamp":" 947805342356"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 5a4a5ea4-7ade-46fc-a436-d82a16101216"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805343302","data":{"timestamp":" 947805343302"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 5a4a5ea4-7ade-46fc-a436-d82a16101216"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805346141","data":{"timestamp":" 947805346141"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 5a4a5ea4-7ade-46fc-a436-d82a16101216"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805347175","data":{"timestamp":" 947805347175"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 5a4a5ea4-7ade-46fc-a436-d82a16101216"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805347649","data":{"timestamp":" 947805347649"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 5a4a5ea4-7ade-46fc-a436-d82a16101216"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805352192","data":{"timestamp":" 947805352192"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 5a4a5ea4-7ade-46fc-a436-d82a16101216"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805352306","data":{"timestamp":" 947805352306"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 5a4a5ea4-7ade-46fc-a436-d82a16101216"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805363479","data":{"timestamp":" 947805363479"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 5a4a5ea4-7ade-46fc-a436-d82a16101216"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805379418","data":{"timestamp":" 947805379416"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 5a4a5ea4-7ade-46fc-a436-d82a16101216"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805399464","data":{"timestamp":" 947805399463"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 5a4a5ea4-7ade-46fc-a436-d82a16101216"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805443471","data":{"timestamp":" 947805443471"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 5a4a5ea4-7ade-46fc-a436-d82a16101216"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805454356","data":{"timestamp":" 947805454356"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 5a4a5ea4-7ade-46fc-a436-d82a16101216"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805485000","data":{"timestamp":" 947805485000"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 15073b3f-95a9-41d2-83e0-72f13248cd4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805485225","data":{"timestamp":" 947805485224"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 15073b3f-95a9-41d2-83e0-72f13248cd4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805486190","data":{"timestamp":" 947805486189"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 15073b3f-95a9-41d2-83e0-72f13248cd4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805487466","data":{"timestamp":" 947805487466"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 15073b3f-95a9-41d2-83e0-72f13248cd4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805490379","data":{"timestamp":" 947805490379"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 15073b3f-95a9-41d2-83e0-72f13248cd4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805491224","data":{"timestamp":" 947805491224"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 15073b3f-95a9-41d2-83e0-72f13248cd4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805491552","data":{"timestamp":" 947805491552"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 15073b3f-95a9-41d2-83e0-72f13248cd4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805492787","data":{"timestamp":" 947805492787"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 15073b3f-95a9-41d2-83e0-72f13248cd4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805496300","data":{"timestamp":" 947805496300"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 15073b3f-95a9-41d2-83e0-72f13248cd4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805497288","data":{"timestamp":" 947805497287"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 15073b3f-95a9-41d2-83e0-72f13248cd4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805497545","data":{"timestamp":" 947805497544"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 15073b3f-95a9-41d2-83e0-72f13248cd4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805498492","data":{"timestamp":" 947805498492"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 15073b3f-95a9-41d2-83e0-72f13248cd4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805501359","data":{"timestamp":" 947805501359"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 15073b3f-95a9-41d2-83e0-72f13248cd4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805502398","data":{"timestamp":" 947805502398"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 15073b3f-95a9-41d2-83e0-72f13248cd4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805502873","data":{"timestamp":" 947805502873"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 15073b3f-95a9-41d2-83e0-72f13248cd4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805507407","data":{"timestamp":" 947805507406"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 15073b3f-95a9-41d2-83e0-72f13248cd4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805507528","data":{"timestamp":" 947805507528"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 15073b3f-95a9-41d2-83e0-72f13248cd4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805526470","data":{"timestamp":" 947805526470"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 32941cff-01d8-42b8-ac95-71be4b859c12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805526710","data":{"timestamp":" 947805526710"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 32941cff-01d8-42b8-ac95-71be4b859c12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805527674","data":{"timestamp":" 947805527674"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 32941cff-01d8-42b8-ac95-71be4b859c12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805528952","data":{"timestamp":" 947805528951"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 32941cff-01d8-42b8-ac95-71be4b859c12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805531890","data":{"timestamp":" 947805531889"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 32941cff-01d8-42b8-ac95-71be4b859c12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805532735","data":{"timestamp":" 947805532735"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 32941cff-01d8-42b8-ac95-71be4b859c12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805533079","data":{"timestamp":" 947805533079"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 32941cff-01d8-42b8-ac95-71be4b859c12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805534314","data":{"timestamp":" 947805534314"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 32941cff-01d8-42b8-ac95-71be4b859c12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805537801","data":{"timestamp":" 947805537800"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 32941cff-01d8-42b8-ac95-71be4b859c12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805538800","data":{"timestamp":" 947805538800"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 32941cff-01d8-42b8-ac95-71be4b859c12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805539063","data":{"timestamp":" 947805539061"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 32941cff-01d8-42b8-ac95-71be4b859c12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805540019","data":{"timestamp":" 947805540019"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 32941cff-01d8-42b8-ac95-71be4b859c12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805542930","data":{"timestamp":" 947805542929"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 32941cff-01d8-42b8-ac95-71be4b859c12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805543965","data":{"timestamp":" 947805543964"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 32941cff-01d8-42b8-ac95-71be4b859c12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805544437","data":{"timestamp":" 947805544437"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 32941cff-01d8-42b8-ac95-71be4b859c12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805548975","data":{"timestamp":" 947805548975"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 32941cff-01d8-42b8-ac95-71be4b859c12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805549097","data":{"timestamp":" 947805549097"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" 32941cff-01d8-42b8-ac95-71be4b859c12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805584245","data":{"timestamp":" 947805584245"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" ce19a064-2aae-47fd-9691-f91c6299405d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_nchi-ng'i-mbi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805598676","data":{"timestamp":" 947805598676"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" ce19a064-2aae-47fd-9691-f91c6299405d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_mbi-ndi-nchi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805603504","data":{"timestamp":" 947805603501"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" ce19a064-2aae-47fd-9691-f91c6299405d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_nji-ri-mbi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805609360","data":{"timestamp":" 947805609360"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" ce19a064-2aae-47fd-9691-f91c6299405d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_twi-mbi-ni"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805615071","data":{"timestamp":" 947805615071"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" ce19a064-2aae-47fd-9691-f91c6299405d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_nyi-mbi-wi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805622050","data":{"timestamp":" 947805622049"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" ce19a064-2aae-47fd-9691-f91c6299405d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_mbi-ji-hi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805635612","data":{"timestamp":" 947805635612"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" ce19a064-2aae-47fd-9691-f91c6299405d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_ng'i-shi-mbi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805651403","data":{"timestamp":" 947805651402"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" ce19a064-2aae-47fd-9691-f91c6299405d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_li-mbi-fi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805660649","data":{"timestamp":" 947805660649"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" ce19a064-2aae-47fd-9691-f91c6299405d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_mbi-fi-vyi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" fi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805671372","data":{"timestamp":" 947805671372"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" ce19a064-2aae-47fd-9691-f91c6299405d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_mbi-fi-vyi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" vyi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805687365","data":{"timestamp":" 947805687365"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" ce19a064-2aae-47fd-9691-f91c6299405d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_mbi-fi-vyi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805705589","data":{"timestamp":" 947805705589"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" ce19a064-2aae-47fd-9691-f91c6299405d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_mbi-nchi-mchi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" nchi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805731611","data":{"timestamp":" 947805731611"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" ce19a064-2aae-47fd-9691-f91c6299405d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_mbi-nchi-mchi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbi"," userResponse":" mbi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947805737438","data":{"timestamp":" 947805737438"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_180622"," gameId":" ce19a064-2aae-47fd-9691-f91c6299405d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_mbi..mbi.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_mbi_mbi-nchi-mchi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}